http://www.scorespro.com/privacy/

All Matches
Live ()
Select your timezone: Fri 11 Dec 07:47 GMT +02
Select a timezone from the list. Chosen options need to be adjusted to the daylight saving time manually.
Welcome to the privacy policy of ScoresPro.com
This privacy policy was last updated on 20 May 2018.
ScoresPro.com are committed to your privacy.
The terms detailed below are the basis on which we hold personal information about you.
PERSONAL INFORMATION - COLLECTION
As a visitor to the Site, you can engage in many activities without providing any Personal Information.
We do not collect your personal information when you simply browse our website. During the process of delivering an information
to you via our website, ScoresPro.com does not collect any personally identifiable information about you such as name, address, phone number, or e-mail address etc...
For the time being we do not require personal information at all.
However, ScoresPro.com may or may not obtain some types of non-personally identifiable information such as the Internet
Service Provider you use to connect to the Internet, your browser type, the type of computer operating system you use
(Macintosh or Windows, for example), or what screen resolution do you use.
The information collected by ScoresPro.com viaGoogle Analytics* is used for the
purpose of improving your browsing experience on our website.
PERSONAL INFORMATION - CONTACT FORMS
Our Web site's online contact form and/or live chat service requires visitors to give us voluntarily their contact information (like their name, email, etc).
Such information collected from the online contact form and/or live chat service is used only to get in touch with the visitor when necessary and only upon his/her request.
It is in the visitors’ best interest to submit truthful information, as this is used to contact him/her.
If this does occur, ScoresPro.com will never, under no circumstances, use such personal information for any purposes other than
the ones you have provided them for.
PERSONAL INFORMATION - STORAGE
The personal data may be collected by us is only the one provided through contact forms
and will be evaluated periodically to determine whether we should continue to hold it.
PERSONAL INFORMATION - USE OF
We will only use the personal information you may provide to us in the future
only for communicating with you or notifying you of information
relating to our and services.
Personal Information - Disclosure
We do not disclose your personal information to third
parties unless this is required by law. Further
we do not sell, trade or rent your personal information to
others as we'll never do in the future.
We may only provide aggregate statistics about visitors, browsing statistics,
traffic patterns and related site information to reputable
third party vendors but these will not include any personal
identifying information.
COOKIES
ScoresPro.com, as well as most sites on the Internet, uses
"cookies" to enhance your experience on the web.
ScoresPro.com cannot use these cookies to personally identify
you in any way.
A cookie is a small piece of information that is sent to your
browser from a World Wide Web Server.
This block of data can be anything, a unique user ID generated
by the server, the current date and time, the IP Address of
where the browser is logged onto the net or any other chunk
of data that you want.
After a browser receives a cookie it will then send that cookie
to the server that set it whenever it is appropriate and required/requested.
The browser will only send the cookie to the server that originally
set it.
This means that the server can't tell if your browser has
cookies that other sites have sent.
An HTTP Cookie cannot be used to get data from your hard drive,
get your email address or steal sensitive information about
your person.
The ScoresPro.com Web Server(s) will send a Cookie to a Client
system when our adserver serves an ad in order to record unique
ID associated with this ad so that should you decide to click
on the ad, your browserknows which advertiser's web page to
redirect you to.
We may or may not also use cookies to enhance your experience
on our website (personalization,...). We believe cookies to
be harmless, and will eventually be to everyone's benefit
(end users, as well as site builders).
If you do not want the benefit of cookies, there is a simple
procedure to manually delete your cookies. Please consult
your web browser's Help documentation for more information.
Read more about ourCookies Policy
THIRD-PARTY LINKS
This website may include links to third-party websites, plug-ins and/or applications.
Clicking on those links or enabling those connections may allow third parties to collect or share data about you.
We do not control these third-party websites and are not responsible for their privacy statements.
When you leave our website, we encourage you to read the privacy policy of every website you visit or third party mobile application you may use.
INTERNATIONAL TRANSFERS
We do not transfer your information outside the European Economic Area (EEA).
CONTACT DETAILS
ScoresPro Limited, Suite 102, Ground Floor, Blake Building, Eyre & Hutson Streets, BELIZE.
YOUR CONSENT
By using ScoresPro.com (website), you consent to our collection and use of your non personal data for the purposes set out above.
In the event that we decide to change our privacy policy we will post such changes on this page in order that you are
always aware of the information we collect, how we use it and under what circumstances we disclose it.
USA - Major League Soccer (MLS)
Kontinental Hockey League (KHL)
